<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tes on どうも</title>
    <link>https://quixten.github.io/tes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tes on どうも</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 11:06:38 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quixten.github.io/tes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Walk Alone, Strength of Bone</title>
      <link>https://quixten.github.io/tes/walk-alone-strength-of-bone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 11:06:38 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quixten.github.io/tes/walk-alone-strength-of-bone/</guid>
      <description>Wood is too pliant. With every strike accompanied by a simultaneous clink and a defeated clunk, Seraphina pounds out the bigger notches in the blade of her sword on the unsatisfactory anvil of an old crate in her apartment. The jaw of a simple forest wolf should not be so doughty.
Her knees aching from the walk, Sera cursed her neglect in her training. Just about as she surfaced into some idyllic pool clearing where she was already entertaining thoughts of relaxing and recuperating, a not-entirely familiar grumble alerted her to an ambush of local carnivores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Mancies, New Fancies</title>
      <link>https://quixten.github.io/tes/new-mancies-new-fancies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 06:33:52 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quixten.github.io/tes/new-mancies-new-fancies/</guid>
      <description>A letter written by Hjolfr of the Reach to himself
Curious branch of study, logomancy. Strictly speaking, it&amp;rsquo;s the study of the magic of &amp;lsquo;words&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;words&amp;rsquo; here meaning any sound that bears meaning to creatures capable of thought. It is hotly debated whether Thu&amp;rsquo;um is a form of logomancy, or whether it is a form of Tonal Architecture, by the kind of imbeciles that think it must only be a form of one with no aspects of the other, and by the kind of ignoramuses that fail to grasp that the two supercategories whose basics they pretend to grasp are not as separate as they think.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
