<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tes on どうも</title>
    <link>https://quixten.github.io/tes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tes on どうも</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:54:49 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://quixten.github.io/tes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Liches Are</title>
      <link>https://quixten.github.io/tes/what-liches-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:54:49 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://quixten.github.io/tes/what-liches-are/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The greatest of all prey for a witchhunter, a knight, an inquisitor, or any of the other ways one might align their fates in the correction of great evils, is the lich; a lich being nothing more or less than a person whose mortality is deferred by the creation of a phylactery, a vessel which they, through a great working of physic and magic, impregnate with their soul, freshly amputated from their living body, granting them unending unlife until such time as their phylactery is broke open or their magical working is through strange circumstance unraveled.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Land of All Trees (song, WIP)</title>
      <link>https://quixten.github.io/tes/land-of-all-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 16:06:18 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://quixten.github.io/tes/land-of-all-trees/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;chorus&#34;&gt;Chorus:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Home of mine, thou storied hall,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;No country boasts green trees so tall,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;From greatest spruce, to shrub most mean,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Thou show&amp;rsquo;st me ever greener green,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Though long my tooth may ere I go,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;All thy sights, I&amp;rsquo;ll never know,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Oh carpets soft, and dewdrink good,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;My land of all trees, Valenwood.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;verse-birch&#34;&gt;Verse (Birch):&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With bark of alabaster white,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Your branches reach with meagre might,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;A trusty trunk, a wholesome shade,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Birch, the forest&amp;rsquo;s collonnade.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Queer Meeting</title>
      <link>https://quixten.github.io/tes/a-queer-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 12:56:22 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://quixten.github.io/tes/a-queer-meeting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For a lover of long, rambling walks, the enormous complex of tunnels and outposts the Dwemer carved into the Southern mountain ranges of Skyrim are the perfect retreat, and having a base in Athamez gives Hjolfr unparalleled access. For all he&amp;rsquo;s explored though, he mayn&amp;rsquo;t have ever been this far East in them. He reckons that he might have made it all the way out to the Jeralls South of the Rift.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walk Alone, Strength of Bone</title>
      <link>https://quixten.github.io/tes/walk-alone-strength-of-bone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 11:06:38 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://quixten.github.io/tes/walk-alone-strength-of-bone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wood is too pliant. With every strike accompanied by a simultaneous clink and a defeated clunk, Seraphina pounds out the bigger notches in the blade of her sword on the unsatisfactory anvil of an old crate in her apartment. The jaw of a simple forest wolf should not be so doughty.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Her knees aching from the walk, Sera cursed her neglect in her training. Just about as she surfaced into some idyllic pool clearing where she was already entertaining thoughts of relaxing and recuperating, a not-entirely familiar grumble alerted her to an ambush of local carnivores. There were three of them. Grey as the stone of Fort Alessia, fur matted and filthy, they stirred from their daze near the pool and sized her up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mancies, New Fancies</title>
      <link>https://quixten.github.io/tes/new-mancies-new-fancies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 06:33:52 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://quixten.github.io/tes/new-mancies-new-fancies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A letter written by Hjolfr of the Reach to himself&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Curious branch of study, logomancy. Strictly speaking, it&amp;rsquo;s the study of the magic of &amp;lsquo;words&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;words&amp;rsquo; here meaning any sound that bears meaning to creatures capable of thought. It is hotly debated whether Thu&amp;rsquo;um is a form of logomancy, or whether it is a form of Tonal Architecture, by the kind of imbeciles that think it must only be a form of one with no aspects of the other, and by the kind of ignoramuses that fail to grasp that the two supercategories whose basics they pretend to grasp are not as separate as they think. No, the Thu&amp;rsquo;um is ruled nearly as inexorably by the pure, belting, bellowing Tones of its practitioners as it is by the Meanings the ancient words of the Dragons carry, and the Tones of my original specialty are fairly &lt;em&gt;laced&lt;/em&gt; with socially and epigenetically constructed meaning, in much the same way that the color of a set of curtains is.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
